Edwin Way Teale Papers 1981.0009
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series XIII: Photographs, undated, 1860s-1990s
  - Subseries E: Personal Photographs, 1860-1990s (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_d637db3c5fe3bd6b25e5db02cf27471d)
    - David Teale (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_3a6014e15564a0833b6bbfe5dd8e56b5)
      - mid 1930s - late 1930s (Box 393:, Folder 7263-7264)
      - late 1930s (Box 393:, Folder 7265)
      - early 1940s (Box 393:, Folder 7266-7269)
      - [1944] (Box 393:, Folder 7270-7277)
    - Edwin Way Teale and Nellie Teale (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_2c5d91f325ebb68d69eed3d05f020142)
      - 1920s (Box 395:, Folder 7278)
      - 1930s (Box 395:, Folder 7279)
      - 1940s (Box 395:, Folder 7280)
      - 1950s (Box 395:, Folder 7281)
      - 1960s (Box 395:, Folder 7282)
      - 1960s (Box 396:, Folder 7283-7284)
      - 1970s (Box 396:, Folder 7285)
    - Edwin Way Teale (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_52560a54a8cb75aa4a11209c2bdbe4c0)
      - 1901 (Box 397:, Folder 7286)
      - 1902-1912 (Box 397:, Folder 7287)
      - 1915 (Box 397:, Folder 7288-7290)
      - 1916 (Box 397:, Folder 7291)
      - 1917 (Box 397:, Folder 7292)
      - 1918 (Box 397:, Folder 7293-7296)
      - 1920 (Box 397:, Folder 7297)
      - 1920s (Box 397:, Folder 7298-7299)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 397:, Folder 7300)
      - 1923 (Box 397:, Folder 7301-7303)
      - 1925 (Box 398:, Folder 7304-7305)
      - 1926 (Box 398:, Folder 7306)
      - 1926 (Box 398:, Folder 7307-7308)
      - 1930s (Box 398:, Folder 7309-7315)
      - 1930s, 1981-0009/SeriesXIIIPhotographs/SubseriesEPersonalPhotographs/Box399:7316-7323 (Box 399, Folder 7316-7323)
        Authors; Naturalists
      - 1930s, 1981-0009/SeriesXIII/SubseriesE/Box400:7324-7332 (Box 400:, Folder 7324-7332)
      - early 1940s (Box 400:, Folder 7326-7331)
      - mid 1940s (Box 400:, Folder 7332)
      - mid 1940s (Box 401:, Folder 7333-7337)
      - late 1940s (Box 401:, Folder 7338-7341)
      - early 1950s (Box 402:, Folder 7342-7348)
      - mid 1950s (Box 402:, Folder 7349-7351)
      - mid 1950s (Box 403:, Folder 7352-7359)
      - late 1950s (Box 404:, Folder 7360-7364)
      - early 1960s (Box 404:, Folder 7365-7368)
      - early 1960s (Box 405:, Folder 7369)
      - mid 1960s (Box 405:, Folder 7370-7377)
      - mid 1960s (Box 406:, Folder 7378-7385)
      - mid 1960s (Box 407:, Folder 7386)
      - late 1960s (Box 407:, Folder 7387-7392)
      - 1970s (Box 407:, Folder 7393-7494)
      - 1970s (Box 408:, Folder 7395-7403)
      - 1970s (Box 409:, Folder 7404-7410)
      - late 1970s (Box 409:, Folder 7411-7412)
      - late 1970s (Box 409:, Folder 7413-7415)
    - Family (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_b5b8442e111affb3c23b83e357ac1458)
      - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_041f54d1e95a8fb4aa852c72eb494e13)
        - Unidentified People (Box 411:, Folder 7416)
      - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_5b54bddbaad0da05db146a7889f2fd5a)
        - Grace Bishop Phillips-Gould, 1881 August 11 (Box 407:, Folder 7417)
        - Nellie Electa Phillips, 1882 June 30 (Box 407:, Folder 7418)
        - Nellie Electa and Clifford Phillips, 1885 (Box 407:, Folder 7419)
        - Clara Way Teale, 1880 (Box 407:, Folder 7420)
        - Haigh Teale (Box 407:, Folder 7421)
        - Jeptha and Ellen Teale (Box 407:, Folder 7422)
        - Oliver Teale, early 1880s (Box 407:, Folder 7423)
        - Oliver Teale (Box 411:, Folder 7424)
        - Edwin Franklin Way (Box 411:, Folder 7425)
        - Unidentified People, late 1880s (Box 411:, Folder 7426)
      - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_382797588b6023d94d6f5dd8c36b38c2)
        - Frederick Donovan (Box 411:, Folder 7427)
        - Grace (Bishop) Phillips (Box 411:, Folder 7428)
        - Nellie Electa Phillips, [1892] (Box 411:, Folder 7429)
        - Nellie Electa Phillips, [1895] (Box 411:, Folder 7430)
        - Nellie Electa Phillips, 1890 June 30 (Box 411:, Folder 7431)
        - Nellie Electa Phillips, 1895 (Box 411:, Folder 7432)
        - Nellie Electa Phillips (Box 411:, Folder 7433)
        - Clara Teale (Box 407:, Folder 7434)
        - Kathryn Mae Teale (Box 407:, Folder 7435)
        - Oliver Teale, 1892 (Box 407:, Folder 7436)
        - Unidentified Child, late 1890s (Box 407:, Folder 7437)
        - Unidentified Woman, late 1890s (Box 407:, Folder 7438)
        - Unidentified People (Box 407:, Folder 7439-7440)
        - Allen Way (Box 411:, Folder 7441)
        - Oliver Teale, 1894 (Box 411:, Folder 7442)
      - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_a9f4bc79cfb8d4fa36a4b52ef69c7fed)
        - Nellie Electa Phillips, [1900] (Box 412:, Folder 7442)
        - Oliver Teale (Box 412:, Folder 7443)
        - Unidentified People (Box 412:, Folder 7444)
        - Edwin F. and Jemima Way (Box 412:, Folder 7445)
        - Hiram Way's Family (Box 412:, Folder 7446)
        - Winnifred and Betty Way (Box 412:, Folder 7447)
      - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_b40aa5d79faff5129fef90ad9b7e1d07)
        - Susie (Edwards) and Henry Bogue (Box 412:, Folder 7448)
        - Betty and Phyllis Edwards (Box 412:, Folder 7449)
        - "Aunty" Furnas, 1913 (Box 412:, Folder 7450)
        - Grace Bishop Phillips-Gould (Box 412:, Folder 7451)
        - Clifford and Mabel Phillips (Box 412:, Folder 7452)
        - Scrapbook, 1910 (Box 412:, Folder 7453-7455)
        - Clara Way Teale (Box 407:, Folder 7456-7457)
        - Kathryne Mae Teale (Box 407:, Folder 7458)
        - Unidentified Child, 1913 (Box 407:, Folder 7459)
        - Unidentified People (Box 407:, Folder 7460-7463)
        - Winnifred Way (Box 412:, Folder 7464)
      - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_7e07013be8edc027b9add0880fde37ae)
        - Susie (Edwards) and Henry Bogue (Box 413:, Folder 7465)
        - Bradford Donovan (Box 413:, Folder 7466)
        - Phyllis and Betty Edwards (Box 413:, Folder 7467)
        - Phyllis Edwards (Box 413:, Folder 7468)
        - Lois (Edwards) Fudge (Box 413:, Folder 7469)
        - Helen Louise Larrance (Box 413:, Folder 7470)
        - Miriam (Furnas) Larrance's Family (Box 413:, Folder 7471)
        - Clifford and Mabel Phillips (Box 413:, Folder 7472)
        - Scrapbook (Box 413:, Folder 7473)
        - Clara Way Teale (Box 413:, Folder 7474-7475)
        - Unidentified People (Box 413:, Folder 7476-7481)
        - Edwin F. and Jemima Way (Box 413:, Folder 7482-7483)
        - Winnifred Way (Box 413:, Folder 7484)
      - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_cb982cc98bcbe9a57e08399cb8ae95e2)
        - Della Sue, Benny, Mary, and Barbara (Box 413:, Folder 7485)
        - Bradford Donovan (Box 413:, Folder 7486)
        - Frederick Donovan (Box 413:, Folder 7487)
        - Phyllis Edwards (Box 413:, Folder 7488)
        - Lois (Edwards) Fudge (Box 413:, Folder 7489)
        - Jack and Renée Kimmich (Box 413:, Folder 7490)
        - Glenn Payne's Family (Box 413:, Folder 7491)
        - Nellie Phillips Scott's Children (Box 413:, Folder 7492)
        - Shirley and Phil Scott, 1930 (Box 413:, Folder 7493)
        - Clara Way Teale (Box 414:, Folder 7494-7495)
        - Unidentified People (Box 414:, Folder 7496)
        - Jemima Way (Box 414:, Folder 7497-7499)
      - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_a81a1858c10cac6d108846aee3bf0de0)
        - Frances Lea Chambers, 1947 (Box 414:, Folder 7500)
        - Betty and Fran Edwards, 1947 (Box 414:, Folder 7501)
        - Kathyrine Fudge, 1946 (Box 414:, Folder 7502)
        - Kathyrine Fudge (Box 414:, Folder 7503)
        - S.J. Guenther, 1946 (Box 414:, Folder 7504)
        - Miriam (Furnas) Larrance's Family, 1947 (Box 414:, Folder 7505)
        - Pamela Rea (Box 414:, Folder 7506)
        - Nellie Phillips Scott's Family, 1942 (Box 414:, Folder 7507)
        - Clara Way Teale (Box 414:, Folder 7508)
      - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_e2ad6646a43a20c11be580bb116a112f)
        - Lois (Edwards) and Kathyrine Fudge, 1951 (Box 414:, Folder 7509)
        - Jean Larrance's Family, 1950 (Box 414:, Folder 7510)
        - Jean, Elizabeth, Helen Louise, Marianne Larrance (Box 414:, Folder 7511)
        - Clifford Phillips' Family, 1953 (Box 414:, Folder 7512)
        - Pamela Rea (Box 414:, Folder 7513)
        - Phyllis (Edwards) and Pamela Rea, 1957 (Box 414:, Folder 7514)
        - Clara Teale (Box 414:, Folder 7515)
      - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_122e1c652a3b6858ce8f70470b19c2d8)
        - Phyllis Edwards, 1961 (Box 414:, Folder 7516)
    - Nellie Teale (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_3a128374d0af169697acbec0a858c454)
      - 1900 (Box 415:, Folder 7517)
      - 1900s (Box 415:, Folder 7518-7519)
      - 1905-1910 (Box 415:, Folder 7520-7521)
      - 1910s (Box 415:, Folder 7522-7523)
      - 1920s (Box 415:, Folder 7524-7531)
      - Nellie with Clara, Jemima, and David, 1920s (Box 415:, Folder 7532)
      - 1930s (Box 416:, Folder 7533-7535)
      - 1940s (Box 416:, Folder 7536-7542)
      - 1950s (Box 416:, Folder 7543-7546)
      - 1950s (Box 417:, Folder 7547)
      - early 1960s (Box 417:, Folder 7548-7551)
      - mid 1960s (Box 417:, Folder 7552-7554)
      - mid 1960s (Box 418:, Folder 7555)
      - late 1960s (Box 418:, Folder 7556-7557)
      - 1970s (Box 418:, Folder 7558-7563)
      - 1970s (Box 419:, Folder 7564-7570)
    - Other Prints (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_c7c011e6a2aff724c113d995a8a8b28d)
      - Other Prints (Box 420:, Folder 7571-7572)
      - by Leslie O. Anderson (Box 420:, Folder 7573)
      - by Warren Boyer (Box 420:, Folder 7574)
      - by Brown Brothers (Box 420:, Folder 7575)
      - by Clyde Fisher (Box 420:, Folder 7576)
      - by Phillip O. Gravelle (Box 420:, Folder 7577)
      - by Andrew Halbran (Box 420:, Folder 7578)
      - by Seymour Hill (Box 420:, Folder 7579)
      - by Bert Inman (Box 420:, Folder 7580)
      - by Henry B. Kane (Box 420:, Folder 7581)
      - by Larson Kans (Box 420:, Folder 7582)
      - by Edwin Levick (Box 420:, Folder 7583)
      - by Muller (Box 420:, Folder 7584)
      - by National Broadcasting Company (Box 420:, Folder 7585)
      - by Leslie Pelitier (Box 420:, Folder 7586)
      - by Schoonhals (Box 420:, Folder 7587)
      - by Signal Corps Pictorial Service (Box 420:, Folder 7588)
      - by David Teale (Box 420:, Folder 7589-7593)
      - by W.E. Teale (Box 420:, Folder 7594)
      - by Unidentified Photographer (Box 420:, Folder 7595-7604)
      - by U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 420:, Folder 7605)
      - by Virginia Welch (Box 420:, Folder 7606-7609)
      - by Wide World Photos (Box 420:, Folder 7610)
      - of Greeting Cards (Box 420:, Folder 7611)
      - of Houses (Box 420:, Folder 7612)
      - of Trains (Box 420:, Folder 7613)
    - Oversize Prints (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_408f62590ff94e1e9a6c48ec91e1713d)
      - David Teale, 1940s (Box 377:, Folder 6913)
      - Edwin Way Teale, 1918 (Box 377:, Folder 6914)
      - Edwin Way Teale, 1950s (Box 377:, Folder 6915)
      - Edwin Way Teale, 1940s (Box 377:, Folder 6916)
      - Edwin Way Teale, 1930s (Box 377:, Folder 6917)
      - Edwin with Oliver and Clara Teale, 1910s (Box 377:, Folder 6918)
      - Edwin with Nellie Teale, 1970s (Box 377:, Folder 6919)
      - Nellie Teale, 1910s (Box 377:, Folder 6920)
      - Other Prints (by Unidentified Artists) (Box 377:, Folder 6921)
      - by Doris Schleisner, 1963 (Box 377:, Folder 6922-6923)
      - by Unidentified Photographer (Box 377:, Folder 6924)
  - Subseries F: John Burroughs Related Material, 1922-1960s (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_feea10c7004b365516189b4f83e3b86b)
    Contains 430 negatives and 110 prints that feature John Burroughs' house, property, and relatives. The 3" x 5" negatives are accompanied by a written guide. The prints are arranged by the photographer's name.
    - Prints (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_f8efaa0a14fef3454244407dfb780c7f)
      - by Frank Chapman (Box 421:, Folder 7614)
      - by Clyde Fisher (Box 421:, Folder 7615-7617)
      - by Inez Haring (Box 421:, Folder 7618)
      - by J.D. Johnson (Box 421:, Folder 7619)
      - by R.H. Macy (Box 421:, Folder 7620)
      - by C.O. Sutton (Box 421:, Folder 7621)
      - by Edwin Way Teale (Box 421:, Folder 7622)
      - by Unidentified Photographer (Box 421:, Folder 7623-7624)
    - Negatives (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_e5f33a5833f70f2c53655a8a5ddecacf)
      - Envelope 1, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7625)
      - Envelope 2, 1925 (Box 422:, Folder 7626)
      - Envelope 3, 1924 (Box 422:, Folder 7627)
      - Envelope 4, 1924 (Box 422:, Folder 7628)
      - Envelope 5, 1925 (Box 422:, Folder 7629)
      - Envelope 6, 1926 (Box 422:, Folder 7630)
      - Envelope 7, 1924 (Box 422:, Folder 7631)
      - Envelope 8, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7632)
      - Envelope 9, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7633)
      - Envelope 10, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7634)
      - Envelope 12, 1930 (Box 422:, Folder 7635)
      - Envelope 13, 1926 (Box 422:, Folder 7636)
      - Envelope 14, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7637)
      - Envelope 15, 1925 (Box 422:, Folder 7638)
      - Envelope 16, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7639)
      - Envelope 17, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7640)
      - Envelope 18, 1924 (Box 422:, Folder 7641)
      - Envelope 19, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7642)
      - Envelope 20, 1927 (Box 422:, Folder 7643)
      - Envelope 21, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7644)
      - Envelope 22, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7645)
      - Envelope 23, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7646)
      - Envelope 24, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7647)
      - Envelope 25, 1925 (Box 422:, Folder 7648)
      - Envelope 26, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7649)
      - Envelope 27, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7650)
      - Envelope 28, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7651)
      - Envelope 29, 1927 (Box 422:, Folder 7652)
      - Envelope 30, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7653)
      - Envelope 31, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7654)
      - Envelope 32, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7655)
      - Envelope 33, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7656)
      - Envelope 34, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7657)
      - Envelope 35, 1925 (Box 422:, Folder 7658)
      - Envelope 36, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7659)
      - Envelope 37, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7660)
      - Envelope 38, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7661)
      - Envelope 39, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7662)
      - Envelope 40, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7663)
      - Envelope 41, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7664)
      - Envelope 42, 1926 (Box 422:, Folder 7665)
      - Envelope 43, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7666)
      - Envelope 44, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7667)
      - Envelope 45, 1926 (Box 422:, Folder 7668)
      - Envelope 46, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7669)
      - Envelope 47, 1926 (Box 422:, Folder 7670)
      - Envelope 48, 1926 (Box 422:, Folder 7671)
      - Envelope 49, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7672)
      - Envelope 50, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7673)
      - Envelope 51, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7674)
      - Envelope 52, 1926 (Box 422:, Folder 7675)
      - Envelope 53, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7676)
      - Envelope 54, 1925 (Box 422:, Folder 7677)
      - Envelope 55, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7678)
      - Envelope 56, 1925 (Box 422:, Folder 7679)
      - Envelope 57, 1929 (Box 422:, Folder 7680)
      - Envelope 58, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7681)
      - Envelope 59, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7682)
      - Envelope 60, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7683)
      - Envelope 61, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7684)
      - Envelope 62, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7685)
      - Envelope 63, 1924 (Box 422:, Folder 7686)
      - Envelope 64, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7687)
      - Envelope 65, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7688)
      - Envelope 66, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7689)
      - Envelope 67, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7690)
      - Envelope 68, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7691)
      - Envelope 69, 1925 (Box 422:, Folder 7692)
      - Envelope 70, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7693)
      - Envelope 71, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7694)
      - Envelope 72, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7695)
      - Envelope 73, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7696)
      - Envelope 74, 1927 (Box 422:, Folder 7697)
      - Envelope 75, 1927 (Box 422:, Folder 7698)
      - Envelope 76, 1927 (Box 422:, Folder 7699)
      - Envelope 77, 1930 (Box 422:, Folder 7700)
      - Envelope 78, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7701)
      - Envelope 79, 1928 (Box 422:, Folder 7702)
      - Concord, Mass, 1922 (Box 422:, Folder 7703-7709)
      - Julian, undated (Box 422:, Folder 7710)